Hirwa Jean Eric

I am a self-motivated designer and software developer.

Location: Kigali city, Rwanda
Email: hirwajeric@gmail.com
Phone: +250 780 599 859



I am a self-motivated developer and designer with special skill in Software Project Management and documentation.

My goals in software development and design are to make software and designs that express people's values and meet their goals.

I am equipped with knowledge and experience in a number of programming languages like Java, C, JavaScript and design software as it is on the list of my professional skills.

Work Experience

Freelance Developer

Kigali

June 2022 to Present

I have been developing web apps using M.E.R.N (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js)

Freelancer Graphic Designer

Hempress Restaurant - Kigali September 2019 to September 2019

My Job was to design them a logo and menu, print them in addition of fliers.

Education

Bachelors in Information Technology, Major in Software Engineering.

Adventist University of Central Africa - Kigali

September 2018 to Present

A'Level Secondary Education in Physics, Mathematics and Chemistry

Ecole des sciences de Musanze - Northern Province, Musanze District

O'Level Secondary Education

Petit Seminaire Saint Vince de Paul, Ndera - Kigali, Gasabo January 2011 to October 2013

Skills

- WordPress Design and Development (2 years)
- Graphic design (4 years)
- HTML and CSS (4 years)
- Java Programming (2 years)
- Content creation (3 years)
- Software development (1 year)
- MySQL (3 years)
- Git (2 years)
- Branding (3 years)
- JavaScript (1 year)
- REST (1 year)
- C (1 year)

- Linux (2 years)
- GitHub (2 years)
- Hibernate (2 years)
- React (Less than 1 year)
- Node.js (Less than 1 year)
- Express.js (Less than 1 year)
- MongoDB (Less than 1 year)
- JSON
- APIs
- Unit Testing
- Application Development

Languages

- English Fluent
- French Intermediate
- Kinyarwanda Native

Certifications and Licenses

Graphic Design

April 2018 to August 2018 A graphic Design Certificate

Links

GitHub account: https://github.com/hirwajeaneric/

Portfolio: https://hirwajeaneric.netlify.app/